<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="44">

<page id="390007" title="Sector Names" descr="0" voice="yes">
 <t id="30066">{7,1020218} {12,101}(Getsu Fune beta)</t> 
</page>

<page id="391900">
 <t id="1600">5000</t>
 <t id="1601">100000</t>
 <t id="1602">450</t>
 <t id="1700">Buster \(M4\)</t>
 <t id="1701">Buster + Mercury</t>
 <t id="1702">Buster \(M4\)</t>
</page>

<page id="399619">
 <t id="10004">Reunion</t>
 <t id="10005">Take on the role of Julian Brenham while you continue the fight against the Kha'ak and eventually reunite the universe with Earth.</t>
</page>

<page id="399620">
 <t id="20000">Guild Starts</t>
 <t id="20001">A collection of starts where you are part of one of the guilds</t>
 <t id="20010">Bounty Hunters Guild</t>
 <t id="20011">Having operated independently as a freelancer for years, you've opted to advance your career by affiliating with the Bounty Hunters Guild, aspiring to emulate your childhood hero, as the greatest hunter ever.</t>
 <t id="20012">Not overly difficult</t>
 <t id="20013">Gu t'Tn</t>
 <t id="20014">Bounty Hunter</t>
 <t id="20015">24</t>
 <t id="20016">500000</t>
 <t id="20017">Mamba</t>
 <t id="20020">Assassins Guild</t>
 <t id="20021">After severing ties with your pirate clan due to irreconcilable differences and carrying out the decisive act of eliminating their leader, your actions draw the attention of the Assassins Guild, who decides to enlist you.</t>
 <t id="20022">Quite Challenging</t>
 <t id="20023">Ninu Claassen</t>
 <t id="20024">Assassin \(Pirate\)</t>
 <t id="20025">39</t>
 <t id="20026">100000</t>
 <t id="20027">Nightshade \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="20030">Celestial Navigators Guild</t>
 <t id="20031">Embracing the legacy of your mother, you choose the path of a celestial navigator. Driven by the belief that you can usher in peace to the galaxy, you set forth on your quest to ascend to the pinnacle of your chosen profession.</t>
 <t id="20032">Relatively straightforward</t>
 <t id="20033">Suli Do</t>
 <t id="20034">Navigator \(Boron\)</t>
 <t id="20035">15</t>
 <t id="20036">850000</t>
 <t id="20037">Angel</t>
 <t id="20040">Merchants Guild</t>
 <t id="20041">Carrying on the legacy of the Guild's Founder, you embark on the journey to establish your expansive trading empire.</t>
 <t id="20042">Mostly easy</t>
 <t id="20043">Wegoras Towisaris Dasinos XIII</t>
 <t id="20044">Merchant \(Teladi\)</t>
 <t id="20045">35</t>
 <t id="20046">350000</t>
 <t id="20047">Logich \(TS\)</t>
 <t id="20100">Argon Military Cadet</t>
 <t id="20101">Emerging as a recent graduate from Argon Military Cadet training, you now embark on the inaugural steps of your promising career.  This start includes an indroductory story plot.</t>
 <t id="20102">Normal</t>
 <t id="20103">Pok Cruise</t>
 <t id="20104">Argon Cadet</t>
 <t id="20105">19</t>
 <t id="20106">10000</t>
 <t id="20107">Discoverer \(M5\)</t>
 <t id="20110">Privateer Warrior</t>
 <t id="20111">After living in Farpoint Omega for most of your life, you embark on your new journey as a fighter pilot for the Privateer Independence Alliance.</t>
 <t id="20112">Simple</t>
 <t id="20113">Sayreen Bro</t>
 <t id="20114">Privateer</t>
 <t id="20115">17</t>
 <t id="20116">5000</t>
 <t id="20117">Privateer M4</t>
 <t id="20120">Privateer Merchant</t>
 <t id="20121">Embarking on a new venture, you, as a modest merchant, commence your journey as a trader affiliated with the Privateer Independence Alliance.</t>
 <t id="20122">Simple</t>
 <t id="20123">Hanes Pareii</t>
 <t id="20124">Privateer</t>
 <t id="20125">26</t>
 <t id="20126">10000</t>
 <t id="20127">Mercury \(TS\)</t>
 <t id="20130">Merceneries Guild</t>
 <t id="20131">Disillusioned by your family's military careers, you chose a different path and became a gun for hire, joining the Mercenaries Guild.</t> 
 <t id="20132">Average</t>
 <t id="20133">Lu t'Tn</t>
 <t id="20134">Mercenary \(Split\)</t>
 <t id="20135">26</t>
 <t id="20136">50000</t>
 <t id="20137">Mercenary Eta \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="30000">Pure Sandbox Starts</t>
 <t id="30001">These start with the universe fully unlocked as if the plots have all been completed, and the plots fully disabled.</t>
 <t id="30010">Argon Fleet Commander</t>
 <t id="30011">Having spent years honing your skills within the Argon Military, you've reached a point where the wealth of knowledge compels you to embark on the journey of establishing your own fleet. </t> 
 <t id="30012">Too Easy</t>
 <t id="30013">Neol Cheram</t>
 <t id="30014">Aron</t>
 <t id="30015">48</t>
 <t id="30016">2000000</t>
 <t id="30017">Nova Vanguard \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="30026">2000</t>
 <t id="30027">Octopus \(M5\)</t>
 <t id="30030">Lost Colony Pioneer</t>
 <t id="30031">Upon reestablishing contact with the Terrans, you set forth on a voyage into uncharted realms, eager to uncover the marvels that await within the vast expanse of the universe.</t> 
 <t id="30032">Its not hard</t>
 <t id="30033">Marelle Keppel</t>
 <t id="30034">Terran \(Lost Colony\)</t>
 <t id="30035">33</t>
 <t id="30036">100000</t>
 <t id="30037">Kitsune \(M5+\)</t>
 <t id="30040">Teladi Profiteer</t>
 <t id="30041">Pooling all your resources into acquiring a freighter, you embark on a journey to lay the foundation of your trading empire.</t> 
 <t id="30042">Simple</t>
 <t id="30043">Yoyunis Hebalisos Tertasobas X</t>
 <t id="30044">Teladi</t>
 <t id="30045">17</t>
 <t id="30046">20000</t>
 <t id="30047">Moa Armoured Transporter</t>
 <t id="30050">Industritech Industrialist</t>
 <t id="30051">With scarce resources at your disposal, you initiate the establishment of your industrial empire destined to stretch across the cosmos.</t> 
 <t id="30052">Challenging</t>
 <t id="30053">Abmanckussut</t>
 <t id="30054">Industritech</t>
 <t id="30055">41</t>
 <t id="30056">5000</t>
 <t id="30057">Oedipus \(M4+\)</t>
 <t id="30060">Unscrupulous Pirate</t>
 <t id="30061">Born into poverty on a backwater planet, you escaped your harsh upbringing and joined the local pirate clans. Hardened by your youth, you show no mercy and take no prisoners.</t> 
 <t id="30062">Difficult</t>
 <t id="30063">Ho T'Hnk</t>
 <t id="30064">Pirate \(Split\)</t>
 <t id="30065">22</t>
 <t id="30066">10000</t>
 <t id="30067">Mandalay \(M4\)</t>
</page>

</language>