<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<language id="44">

<page id="390035">
 <t id="2174">Unfocussed Jump to(: Sector)</t>
 <t id="2175">Use Unfocussed Jumpdrive</t>
</page>

<page id="390120" title="Polly Voice: Ruth" descr="0" voice="yes">
 <t id="300000">Greetings, pilot. While your contributions to our war efforts have been significant, we now require you to demonstrate your unwavering loyalty to the Terran cause. We have several critical missions for you, all involving strikes against the Argon.</t>
 <t id="300001">Excellent work, pilot. Report back to me for your next assignment.</t>
 <t id="300002">Your next mission involves eliminating high-priority Argon targets. You'll be operating within Argon Core sectors, which will be extremely hostile territory for you.</t>
 <t id="300003">With those targets eliminated, continue supporting our efforts against the Argon.</t>
 <t id="300004">That's it, pilot. Welcome to the Terran war effort.</t>
</page>
<page id="390121" title="Polly Voice: Gregory" descr="0" voice="yes">
 <t id="300000">Greetings, pilot. While your contributions to our war efforts have been significant, we now require you to demonstrate your unwavering loyalty to the Terran cause. We have several critical missions for you, all involving strikes against the Argon.</t>
 <t id="300001">Excellent work, pilot. Report back to me for your next assignment.</t>
 <t id="300002">Your next mission involves eliminating high-priority Argon targets. You'll be operating within Argon Core sectors, which will be extremely hostile territory for you.</t>
 <t id="300003">With those targets eliminated, continue supporting our efforts against the Argon.</t>
 <t id="300004">That's it, pilot. Welcome to the Terran war effort.</t>
</page>

<page id="399619">
 <t id="10">Greetings pilot,\nSince the opening of the Terran sectors, new opportunities have arisen, please join me to discuss further\n\nWhen you're ready, please come find me in \033B</t>
 <t id="11">You have a new opportunity for me?</t>
 <t id="12">My Terran contacts have been looking for new pilots to help out the USC while they look to discover everything commonwealth space has to offer.</t>
 <t id="13">Sounds Good, where do I sign up?</t>
 <t id="14">Seek out the USC officer in Neptune once you have enough notoriety with the Terrans</t>
 <t id="15">Great, I will do just that</t>
 <t id="16">New Opportunities</t>
 <t id="17">Join the United Space Command</t>
 <t id="18">Raise your notoriety with the Terrans and join up with the USC Military Patrols</t>
 <t id="19">Raise Notoriety</t>
 <t id="20">{1266,18} {829,101}</t>
 <t id="21">I wish to join the USC</t>
 <t id="22">Greetings pilot, I'm glad you decided to join us.  I'm registering your ships with the United Space Command.  My commanding officer will be in contact shortly with your first assignment.  Good luck out there</t>
 <t id="23">I will wait with Bated Breath</t>
 <t id="24">Greetings pilot,\nHostilities with the Terrans have reached a breaking point, full scale war is all but inevitable\n\nWe can discuss our response further, come find me in \033B</t>
 <t id="25">Reporting in commander</t>
 <t id="26">Great, just in time pilot.  Are you ready for War? Accepting will change the universe forever</t>
 <t id="27">Yes, lets get to War</t>
 <t id="28">I'm yet ready for war</t>
 <t id="29">Greetings pilot,\nHostilities with the Commonwealth have reached a breaking point, full scale war is all but inevitable\n\nWe can discuss our response further, come find me at \033B{object.name@L3M02.APLink Station}\033X in \033B{sector.name@L3M02.Neptune}\033X</t>
 <t id="30">Reporting in commander</t>
 <t id="31">Great, just in time pilot.  Are you ready for War? Accepting will change the universe forever</t>
 <t id="32">Yes, lets get to War</t>
 <t id="33">I'm not yet ready for war</t>
 <t id="34">Treasure Hunt Hint</t>
 <t id="100">Plots</t>
 <t id="101">Universe State</t>
 <t id="102">Farnham's Legacy</t>
 <t id="103">The Terran Sectors will be disconnected from the main universe, and requiring you to complete the Terran Spy Plot before you can access the Terran sectors.  The Terran Conflict Plot need to be unlocked via the separate link plot.</t>
 <t id="104">Terran Conflict</t>
 <t id="105">The Terran Sectors will be connected via Heretics End and the Terran Conflict plots will be available from the start.  You can still do the Terran Spy Plot to add a second link to the Terrans</t>
 <t id="106">Albion Prelude</t>
 <t id="107">The universe is in a state of war with conflicts going on in the War Sectors.  The Terran Conflict and Aldrin Plots will not be available during this universe state</t>
 <t id="108">Terran Spy Plot</t>
 <t id="109">Headquarters Plot</t>
 <t id="110">Xenon Hub Plot</t>
 <t id="111">Reunion</t>
 <t id="112">The Terran sectors will be disconnected until you do the Reunion Plot line.</t>
 <t id="1001">Reunion</t>
 <t id="1002">Reunite the Aldrin colony with Earth</t>
 <t id="1003">Resourceful</t>
 <t id="1004">Reactivate the final set of Hub gates</t>
 <t id="1005">Homebase</t>
 <t id="1006">Acquire your personal Headquarters</t>
 <t id="1007">Albion Pride</t>
 <t id="1008">Help shape the future of the Albion system</t>
 <t id="1009">Happy Hippies</t>
 <t id="1010">Help the Honer to rebuild and relocate their temple</t>
 <t id="1011">Exterminator</t>
 <t id="1012">Complete Operation Final Fury</t>
 <t id="1013">Home Sweet Home</t>
 <t id="1014">Complete the New Home Missions</t>
 <t id="1015">X Marks the Spot</t>
 <t id="1016">Complete the Treasure Hunt Campaign</t>
 <t id="1017">Lost Brothers</t>
 <t id="1018">Complete the Aldrin Missions</t>
 <t id="1019">Balance of Power</t>
 <t id="1020">Finish the Balance of Power mission.</t>
 <t id="1021">Tied Ends</t>
 <t id="1022">Complete Operation Loose Ends.</t>
 <t id="1023">Breaking Grounds</t>
 <t id="1024">Claim your own corner of the galaxy.</t>
 <t id="1025">Incorporated</t>
 <t id="1026">Aid a struggling corporation.</t>
 <t id="1027">Dirty Deeds</t>
 <t id="1028">Deal in Shady Business... and live to tell about it.</t>
 <t id="1029">Master the Terran Conflict</t>
 <t id="1030">Complete all the available Terran Conflict plots</t>
 <t id="1031">Albion Prelude</t>
 <t id="1032">Complete all the available Albion Prelude plots</t>
 <t id="1033">Story is Over</t>
 <t id="1034">Complete all the available plots</t>
 <t id="1035">Reunion</t>
 <t id="1036">Complete all the Reunion plot</t>
 <t id="10000">The long wished-for encounter of Earth holds both joy and sorrow for the people. Despite flourishing trade, the clash of the diverse races, cultures and life forms creates new tensions and open conflict that need to be overcome!</t>
 <t id="10001">After the destruction of the Earth Torus, hostility between the Terrans and Commonwealth descend into a full scale war.  Corporations emerge with new technology to reshape the universe.</t>
 <t id="10002">Classic Starts</t>
 <t id="10003">A collection of classic game starts from previous games.  Set during the Terran Conflict</t>
 <t id="10004">Reunion</t>
 <t id="10005">Take on the role of Julian Brenham while you continue the fight against the Kha'ak and eventually reunite the universe with Earth.</t>
 <t id="11001">1000</t>
 <t id="11002">Sabre \(M4\)</t>
 <t id="11011">1000</t>
 <t id="11012">Scimitar \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="11021">2000</t>
 <t id="11022">Elite \(M4+\)</t>
 <t id="11031">1000</t>
 <t id="11032">Buster \(M4\)</t>
 <t id="11041">9000</t>
 <t id="11042">Spitfyre \(M4+\)</t>
 <t id="12001">10000</t>
 <t id="12002">Mercury + Discoverer</t>
 <t id="12011">0</t>
 <t id="12012">Mamba \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="13001">30000</t>
 <t id="13002">Nova Prototype \(M3\)</t>
 <t id="13011">200000</t>
 <t id="13012">Katana \(M6\)</t>
 <t id="13021">2000</t>
 <t id="13022">Harrier Hauler\(M5\)</t>
 <t id="13031">10000</t>
 <t id="13032">Demeter \(TS\)</t>
 <t id="20000">I'm looking to defect</t>
 <t id="20001">I will do as you ask</t>
 <t id="20002">Prove your Loyalty</t>
 <t id="20003">Prove yourself to the Terran cause and strike against the Argon</t>
 <t id="20004">What is my next assignment?</t>
 <t id="20005">Eliminate</t>
 <t id="20006">High-Priority Argon Targets</t>
 <t id="20007">Lower To</t>
 <t id="20008">Terran Double Agent</t>
 <t id="20009">Argon Double Agent</t>
 <t id="20010">Prove yourself to the Argon cause and strike against the Terrans</t>
 <t id="20011">High-Priority Terran Targets</t>
 <t id="50000">Reunion</t>
 <t id="50001">Gamma Patrol</t>
 <t id="50002">Join up with Gamma Patrol and patrol sectors for Kha'ak activity</t>
 <t id="50003">Gamma Patrol Payment</t>
 <t id="50004">Goner Escort</t>
 <t id="50005">Seek out the Goners in their temple and offer assistance</t>
 <t id="50006">Goner Reward Payment</t>
</page>

<page id="393217" title="Albion Prelude HUB Plot" descr="Texts for Albion Prelude HUB Plot Mission." voice="no">
 <t id="100">This is an automated message offering you, an esteemed friend of the Boron and Atreus, the opportunity to work for Atreus Shipbuilding Currents in \033B{sector.name@L2M020.OFantasy}\033X. Please visit us to see what we can offer each other.</t>
 <t id="110">[center][b]Security Details for Hub Reconnection[/b][/center]\n\nThe Hub is to make two connections, between {sector.name@L2M020.OFantasyD} and {sector.name@L2M020.BSnout} and between {sector.name@L2M020.KingdomEndD} and {sector.name@L2M020.RolksDrift}. Atreus is tasked with patrolling {sector.name@L2M020.OFantasyD} and {sector.name@L2M020.BSnout}.\n\nWe believe the Terrans have placed surveillance devices near the gates, which have been left to avoid heightened tensions. We now have clearance to destroy any we encounter. Also be aware of increased Pirate activity reported in neighbouring sectors.\n\n[center][select value='next']Close[/select][/center]</t>
 <t id="113">[center][b]Urgent Bulletin[/b][/center]\n\nA potentially severe situation is developing. The passenger transport on which Boron Researcher {3895,30}(Mahi Ma) was travelling was intercepted by Terran ships while travelling to {sector.name@L2M020.BSnout}. Report indicates that the passengers were captured and the transport scuttled, while the Terrans escaped by Jump Drive.\n\nThe Royal Boron Military Defence Council is currently convening with members of government to prepare an official response which we will broadcast promptly. Additional information can soon be found on Royal Commonwealth News feeds. We have been asked to remind you that the Boron Kingdom is not currently at war with the Terrans and their ships are not to be engaged in Boron space. However, security will be tightened in several key sectors including the Gate Hub.\n\n[center][select value='next']Close[/select][/center]</t>
</page>

<page id="393895" title="Character Lines [TEXT]" descr="0" voice="no">
 <t id="105002">All ships stand ready. The Hub is due to connect between {sector.name@L2M020.OFantasyD} and {sector.name@L2M020.BSnout}.</t>
 <t id="660006">The firewall is penetrated but this command unit can't access the mainframe. The authorisation code isn't accepted. Terraformer unit #cafe also refuses to transmit the current verification code to the superior unit, #efaa. The unknown ship needs to transmit its code and the code of the command unit #efaa to the mainframe of #cafe to unlock it.\n\nCode: {[red]USCMarteen_earth_plus.omega[/red]}</t>
 <t id="660008">Known Code: \033RUSCMarteen_earth_plus.omega\033X</t>
 <t id="660009">To start the hacking process, select the hack option from the #cafe context menu.</t>
</page>

<page id="393212" title="L2 New Home Mission" descr="Mission text for A New Home mission" voice="no">
 <t id="20401">Bola Hi was not in Ocean of Fantasy. I was told that he is in Aldrin. I'll look for him there so he can decode the message from #cafe and we can help with the results.</t>
 <t id="10931">guess how many numbers were correct \(\033Ggreen\033X\), at the false place</t>
 <t id="10932">\(\033Yyellow\033X\) or totally wrong \(\033Rred\033X\). If you need too many guesses, the CPU</t>
 <t id="10955">{3212,10930} {3212,10931} {3212,10932} {3212,10933}</t>
 <t id="10956">Submit current Guess</t>
</page>

<page id="393214" title="L2 Treasure Hunt" descr="Text used in Ketraar's Treasure Hunt MD Mission" voice="no">
 <t id="23">{3214,14}\nFrom the end of the kingdom move one and seven. There is a rock among many, that holds a surprise.\n{actor.name@KTH_toplevel.KTHfirsthintactor}, 10/5/44</t>
 <t id="30">{3214,19}\nOnce you have a firm grasp on where it all began a very, very long time ago, travel until you come to an End: \033RE-S-S-S-S-E-S-W-W-N-W-N-W\033X\n{random.pilot.boron}, 26-11-49</t>
 <t id="31">{3214,20}\nThe journey leads you to a sector in the West. There are not two of them. It can be reached from the South or from the North or with a few jumps, either way you should get home. Once you find it, you will see the light and become the alpha. \033R7  7  18 -5 -12  23 -23  32 4\033X\nThe numbers are the path, {random.pilot.goner} 0-50-0</t>
</page>

<page id="393215" title="version 3.0 Plot Texts" descr="Texts for 3.0 Plot Mission." voice="no">
 <t id="13">Darkspace(name of a faction)</t>
 <t id="41">{1000,50002} Pulsar(ship names from here on)</t>
 <t id="42">{1000,50002} {1000,40004} {17,10861}</t>
 <t id="53">Stephen Torres, Darkspace</t>
 <t id="54">Nils Ryan, Darkspace Covert Operative</t>
 <t id="70">{1000,50002} {1000,130} {17,10841} (more ship names from here on)</t>
 <t id="102">Greetings, pilot. We have another task for you. Please return as soon as you can to the Darkspace Installation.</t>
 <t id="103">Please report back to me at the Darkspace Installation for a further mission briefing.</t>
 <t id="121">Stephen Torres works for a shady organisation called Darkspace. We need him on our side and to use his base for our own operations in the area. Our ultimate aim is to get our hands on some Terran, specifically ATF, tech. This guy is our way in as Darkspace also don't like the ATF much. He's been off the grid for a while, but his name suddenly popped up in some local pirate comms traffic that we intercepted. Since there aren't that many pirate bases in these parts, we expect he's likely to be lurking somewhere in the unknown sectors, north of Oort Cloud. We need you to get over there and locate him. Play it cagey at first, but remember that we want to be his friend.</t>
 <t id="301">Yes, I just got word myself. All is not lost though. We have a lead on the Darkspace guys and we're tracking them down. I need you to make contact with a black market dealer, called Darren We, who can provide us with some much-needed Terran high-tech goods for our experiments.</t>
 <t id="331">It looks like the Darkspace agents have fled to a sector called Maelstrom and have established a pirate base somewhere in the sector. I need you to get over there and rendezvous with Admiral Jarren Hayla, who is leading a Navy task force in that sector. I imagine they could use your help.</t>
 <t id="1301">Find and meet Stephen Torres of Darkspace in {sector.name@L2M015.US1}. We need to gain his trust in order for them to grant us access to their base.</t>
 <t id="1604">Well done! We now have Darkspace on side and Agent Evans is already en route to the Darkspace installation to set up our operation there. You're free to go about your business once more, but we may call on you again when there are further tasks.</t>
 <t id="2501">Defend the Darkspace station from enemy attack!</t>
</page>

<page id="393219" title="Albion Prelude Terran Plot" descr="Terran HQ/HUB Plot, USC lines" voice="no">
 <t id="124">Based on the information Mahi Ma finally revealed, we have found out that the Boron intend on assaulting your HUB in an attempt to capture it for their own use.  We cannot let them get their hands on the HUB so we will do everything in our power to make sure you keep hold of it.</t>
 <t id="125">Hub to {sector.name@L2M022.Segaris} and {sector.name@L2M022.XenonS}</t>
 <t id="126">{player.name}, To make it easier to assault the HUB, we would like you to rearrange the gates to put the HUB between \033B{sector.name@L2M022.Segaris}\033X and \033B{sector.name@L2M022.XenonS}\033X so our ships can get there easily.</t>
 <t id="127">{player.name}, this is Admiral Giorno. During an interrogation session, Mahi Ma revealed very interesting information about the Xenon HUB. We know that you are currently in control of it and there may be a plan in place by the Boron to take it from you.  We must stop this from happening, Report to {object.name@L2M022.SegarisDock} in {7,1021117}, so we can discuss the details of the plan.</t>
 <t id="522">Over recent months, the Boron have undertaken great efforts to encode their research data. While we have the best specialists for decrypting files in the whole universe, even they would need some time to decrypt the HQ data files, time that could be better spent on other things. If you can get information about the Boron encryption algorithm, it would certainly help our researchers.\n\nWhen I monitored Boron fleet movements, I noticed a small Boron group commuting between {7,1020419} and {7,1020716} each week. They don't carry any special wares or personnel, so I believe that it is this group that provides the Argon military with the latest information about the latest Boron research results. They probably also have information in their database that could help our scientists to decode their data.\n\nAs we learned from our previous mission, Boron escorts are not exactly what you would call invincible. So it should be easy for you to convince the Boron to provide you with the data, by one means or another.\n\nGood luck Sir, Sub-Lieutenant Jorwan out.</t>
 <t id="2129">Protect the HUB</t>
 <t id="2130">Rearrange gates on the Hub</t>
</page>

<page id="393223" title="Shady Business" descr="0" voice="no">
 <t id="181">You WILL listen because I am a Planetary Senator. And what the Goners have to say may very well save Earth. Now Read. [Transmit Goner Data]</t>
 <t id="182">You WILL listen because I am a member of the Federation Marshal. And what the Goners have to say may very well save the Federation. Now Read. [Transmit Goner Data]</t>
 <t id="616">The corvette's reactor is unstable. You may be able to track it by radiation signature if you get close enough. I believe you have such a device to detect such low frequencies, it should give the general direction of the derelict.</t>
 <t id="708">This is most excellent news!\n\nFirst you must seek Terran and Argon favor by reaching the notoriety of [yellow]Planetary Senator[/yellow] and [yellow]Federation Marshal[/yellow] respectively.\n\nThen, seek an address with their respective ambassadors and transmit the contents of this data pad to them. There won't be any pointless arguing after they see our rangers' irrefutable proof of the incoming Xenon invasion.\n\nOnce you have picked them both up in a TP class vessel, we will transmit the coordinates of the peace talks. We are keeping it confidential for security reasons. Peace to you my child, may peace be your life.</t>
</page>
</language>